to access your Microsoft Office programs
on a Mac there are three ways you can do
this the first way is you can select the
finder and from there select
applications and then you can scroll
down to find the relevant program so
Word PowerPoint or Excel alternatively
you can do your launchpad and on the
launchpad screen you can then navigate
to where the program icon saw which is
Excel PowerPoint and Word and finally
you can attach the shortcuts to the
programs on your toolbar at the bottom
of the screen as you can see at least
Word Excel and PowerPoint on this bar
for easy access which will then
automatically launch the programs